[Music]
you
okay so that was this morning's
artist her name is Kate oh she's lovely
beautiful absolutely beautiful I know
beautiful music that's right we're busy
with capitalism now so we have this they
released a complete slam front end which
is kind of cool one of the are this
shit's gonna work no understand what
this is bullshit hopefully I won't come
off any more good fix that now let's see
if we make this work
girl admiration is that yerba mate a
talking I don't know man
so you guys see this is like what my
slam fronting looks like it's right here
I always see a lot more if I kept it
over multiple frames but we can switch
up the front end if we can use the super
point pre-training network demo super
fuzzy this gonna work
oh oh oh module object has no attribute
rebuild tensor v2 oh that's that's all
that's great upgrade torch may be newer
torch oh yeah good guess bro okay so
what do you guys think it looks as
shitty as orb actually to be honest my
looks just as good should we modify the
slam to y'all bro no no no hair it's the
same back to my office okay this
actually looks kind of shitty
see if there's like options with our
options I make like the real image
height oh I need - - I've already to put
those before the input oh well that
looks like vaguely better vaguely do we
think these points are better than
I forget how come when is my front end
for this thing over there right like
nothing
did you just a try
no okay yeah I understand they curve it
as a small path my points could do that
too should I have them do that there
should have them do that but a slight
display thing I can just change that if
I make it that big you'll see the whole
thing
[Music]
you
like care about people love that much
empathy is overrated
gross
I did that twice all right there you go
look my nipple long Naoto look I have
long ones
Yeah right look I can do it too maybe I
feel terrible just right this looks like
shit oh wow
okay it's a little bit cheating because
it's going back really far
[Applause]
see the problem
sure in the Pats well so the problem is
just shortening the Pats the problem is
the fact that mine are going back mad
far okay I really could just do
something simple like this only show the
last five frames but it's not really
what we want to do what why is that not
subscript oh oh oh because it's object
just fuck you Python 3 oh yeah
drink twice like that but let's see if
this isn't gonna be what we want really
it's a little closer to what we want but
the problem is that's they have to be
continuous spray there's you think the
simplest way to write that so you can
certainly get the frame IDs you'll see
it we want up to 5 IDs let's say going
back that are contiguous maybe problems
like it can be found in a previous frame
so you see what I'm going for here right
three two zero weight one what do these
things not get out of an order
where do I add the point oh I think I do
okay so now they're in order so now we
check if yeah few months of 0 is not
equal to P 2 then break
sure I mean this looks right right oh
well no no no that's not right
now as long as it's contiguously tract
Wow those points I guess doing such my
projection but still let's look at look
at what super finds output which slim
has a size doesn't use the same size try
that
well like this one like a max back it
can display suicide
yeah it looks like there's a max back in
this plan
is that better Richie's happier
let's actually write this a little bit
less stupidly there's a few ways I can
write this less stupid like
- it
Oh polygon I want like multi line you
don't say polylines this what I want
their points is closed
no so what we want to say is how do you
know
pick up the collar backwards Wow maybe
it's like some of these are only one or
something that seems absolutely right
points array of polygonal curse
Oh disgusting P check factor 2.4 I don't
know what that even means
just let my limiter to five right
looks like your dirty code now the idea
is not not well okay so this checks
completely broke and you guys you got to
catch my shit and Elif ID plus one you
gotta tell me George you're writing bad
code you got to remind me when I forget
to do things like that better oh this is
what polylines probably does
I had to explicitly convert them oh
there we go it's a disgusting read I
know what goes trash
it's not better that's pretty good
looks as good as super point right
yeah I think those matches are all
correct speed on kitty
it looks pro at
and the long ass trails
we'll see I don't think I don't know I
really don't think orbs jumping around
is a big problem like I don't think if
we switch the front end it'll help that
much in China kitty yeah I don't
understand why you can't get that from
the video no huh it's over there
look better ball slow
okay I can't tell I really can't doubt
that is that better than this it's very
similar what you like their colors yeah
okay they have colors out what are the
colors correspond to we can make colors
what do you want College what do you
want colors I can Mike to make colors
let's see what colors Karsten good side
what kind of shitty ass license is this
license a fuck oh my god
release open source code fuck you magic
leave I mean like I appreciate that you
release this but really just so you guys
know twitch slam is MIT licensed you
guys can use it for whatever the hell
you want I don't care
can't sue me though fuck y'all if you
sue me I got lawyers brah is it distance
from optical Center I don't think it is
think it's is that
looks like this one's that color
it's estimated distance to an orbit
pinhole camera do you actually know that
or you might be right no it's a point
confidence heatmap well this is I still
my chat
see I can't even steal their colors I
choose gel their colors
no it's confidence is what they're doing
it's not it's not that we can do the
same thing we really you really want
those colors I know they look kind of
nice don't die
line 16 tracks
cor
whatever track sub one is I don't really
know so it's whatever track sub one is
here
that's the color
they tell me
see what let's see what the map looks
like
coffees
it's actual pretty cool paper we go
distance what kind of distance do you
want
and pick our lives they didn't even use
polylines as shitty coke now I'm mostly
just mad at an open source it like
please please shit under a real open
source license don't be a bitch oh
that's disgusting oh that's gross
looking oh what's line type today blind
type six what's a line type sixteen oh
is that a any Elias line line type is an
invalid keyword for this function
dr. capitalizing T they look just like
eight lies oh they actually don't know
they're a little better very anti
aliased although all those legs look
good oh yeah yeah improve the line
looking
oh that line looks better make lines
look better don't be a bitch that's good
advice in life man but just think about
think about like you know you're about
to do something and you ask the question
like is some Bichir do I think this is
yes don't do it it's like a youtube
channel like thug life advice where they
tell you things like this
tell bro science yeah is the worst it's
hard it's painful it's not arms or chest
or shoulders or even it's like that you
promised yourself last week you were
gonna do it digit but like any true girl
bro you're looking to do a workout
without the world
here's a way to skip leg day guilt-free
faintly injuries its leg dead it all of
a sudden you need stops bothering or you
realize all right you guys are colors I
have a way to get you some colors I
stole some of their code up that's
copyrighted yeah you sue me for cup for
stealing your copyrighted jet we can do
this guy's we can do this
oh you like them look we have callers
now Oh who likes the colors Oh is that
nice
my course fee look pretty cool
how many are there 10 2 3 5 6 8 9 10 I
guess we'll go back to there as well
No
and what God is like color smells so
nice so nice color colors shamelessly
stolen
yeah you say that they are already
excluded pretty well and they're pruned
so we have a pruner that actually prunes
those things
such beauty
oh no my slam front front end is pretty
good oh well okay so we have some
advantage we were using search by
projection I guess they aren't
the times I don't think that trajectory
is like right at all I don't know if
drawing those things takes forever kind
of feels like everything got slower I
mean it shouldn't like that shouldn't be
bad slow alright guys that might be the
stream for today just getting back on
you know I haven't streamed in a while
getting back into being a twitchy look
at Matt stop what those two keyboards
maybe one day we'll do math we'll get
back to riding the optimizer it'll be
kind of fun but what be right today we
wrote colors all the colors are so
pretty well there are you pretty good
kitty let's look at the colors on kitty
oh so pretty oh look at the beauty are
the beautiful colors
Pass is not important only future that's
right oh no actually the colors
correspond to like the match accuracy
the point yeah bro we don't work that
much today bro or if there's hang of the
white paper screenshot had to get hub
you know what why don't want to you run
it screenshot it to your paw request
emergent I am a lazy piece of shit
that's right that's right now you might
be like George you should take your own
advice from earlier in the stream which
is don't be a bitch and do it but nope
nope we're good that we're gonna be a
bitch we're gonna skip leg day that's
right I know yo guys I did yoga last
night this is hardcore wasn't really
that hardcore but like I don't know man
that's what I did last night love your
colors nice it's correct did we actually
turn a little bit and probably I don't
know like points
yeah short video where we add colors
alright guys I go shower I feel kind of
gross and that's it